<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kotatogram Desktop</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Kotatogram Desktop</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:12:00 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kotatogram.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kotatogram 1.4.9 released!</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:12:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-9/</guid><description>This version is released even though isn&amp;rsquo;t fully ready, but there is no other way in current situation.
Download 1.4.9 beta based on Telegram Desktop 3.5.2 Windows Supports Windows 7 and higher. 32-bit installer 32-bit portable 64-bit installer 64-bit portable Linux Supports Ubuntu 18.04 and higher. AppImage Alternative options Please note that update can be delayed. FlatHub page Repology page macOS Supports macOS 10.15 and higher. Download Changes Internal rework of Kotatogram Settings.</description></item><item><title>Kotatogram 1.4.8 released!</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 20:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-8/</guid><description>This release is unexpected, but important because of severe crash in Saved Messages. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t caught it, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck, but it&amp;rsquo;s better to update anyway.
Download 1.4.8 stable based on Telegram Desktop 3.3 Windows Supports Windows 7 and higher. 32-bit installer 32-bit portable 64-bit installer 64-bit portable Linux Supports Ubuntu 18.04 and higher. AppImage Alternative options Please note that update can be delayed. FlatHub page Repology page macOS Supports macOS 10.</description></item><item><title>Kotatogram 1.4.7 released!</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 13:57:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-7/</guid><description>Last release in this year which is needed because who knows what happen if stable branch won&amp;rsquo;t receive update until January 1. Luckily, the &amp;ldquo;make it before January 1&amp;rdquo; thing is not the only point of the release: new features are also in stock.
Download 1.4.7 stable based on Telegram Desktop 3.3 Windows Supports Windows 7 and higher. 32-bit installer 32-bit portable 64-bit installer 64-bit portable Linux Supports Ubuntu 18.04 and higher.</description></item><item><title>Kotatogram 1.4.6 beta released!</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 22:51:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-6/</guid><description>With this version starts the support of sponsored messages from Telegram. I&amp;rsquo;ll remind that it&amp;rsquo;s necessary change because without support of these messages the app is at risk of disabling via API ID. Also all previous version have lost the ability to open the channels with content forwarding and saving restriction enabled. This version supports these channels with support for this restriction.
This version has some known bugs, and there was no time to fix them since there is a need to release as soon as possible.</description></item><item><title>Kotatogram 1.4.5 released!</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 15:12:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-5/</guid><description>This version is not much different from 1.4.4, apart from some bug fixes and moving to stable branch. Stable branch, besides existing crash because of chats with 1 month auto-deletion, now have new problem. Users can&amp;rsquo;t login in this version anymore, and on the top of that there are constant messages that insist on updating.
Download 1.4.5 stable based on Telegram Desktop 3.1.1 Windows Supports Windows 7 and higher. 32-bit installer 32-bit portable 64-bit installer 64-bit portable Linux Supports Ubuntu 16.</description></item><item><title>Kotatogram 1.4.4 beta released!</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:01:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-4/</guid><description>This update needed to be released as soon as possible because of user IDs update in all Telegram apps. But since there is a huge leap from last source update, some things could break, so it&amp;rsquo;s the beta again to make minimal needed tests. If there will no bugs, or they will be easy to fix, this version will be quickly promoted to steable. But this version also has few new features with fixes.</description></item><item><title>Kotatogram 1.4.3 beta released!</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 22:16:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-3/</guid><description>This update is pretty small in features, but it contains some internal work with versioning and updates that allows fasters rebuilds. Also this time I haven&amp;rsquo;t forgot about translations, and Kotatogram even now has German translation.
Download 1.4.3 beta based on Telegram Desktop 2.8.11 Windows Supports Windows 7 and higher. 32-bit installer 32-bit portable 64-bit installer 64-bit portable Linux Supports Ubuntu 16.04 and higher. AppImage Alternative options Please note that update can be delayed.</description></item><item><title>Kotatogram 1.4.2 beta released!</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 21:07:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-2/</guid><description>Since this version caught some beta version commits, the beta has been released. But aside from sources update, there is a few new features and fixes.
Download 1.4.2 beta based on Telegram Desktop 2.8.11 Windows Supports Windows 7 and higher. 32-bit installer 32-bit portable 64-bit installer 64-bit portable Linux Supports Ubuntu 16.04 and higher. AppImage Alternative options Please note that update can be delayed. FlatHub page Repology page macOS Supports macOS 10.</description></item><item><title>Kotatogram 1.4.1 released!</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 13:18:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4-1/</guid><description>This release have no new features, but it has bug fixes. Also this version based on Telegram Desktop 2.7.4, which has scheduled voice chats and payments. More about the update on Telegram site: https://telegram.org/blog/payments-2-0-scheduled-voice-chats
Download stable 1.4.1 based on Telegram Desktop 2.7.4 Windows Supports Windows 7 and higher. 32-bit installer 32-bit portable 64-bit installer 64-bit portable Linux Supports Ubuntu 16.04 and higher. AppImage Alternative options Please note that update can be delayed.</description></item><item><title>Kotatogram 1.4 released!</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:48:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/release-1-4/</guid><description>For a long time this Kotatogram was abandoned. But actually it wasn&amp;rsquo;t, I just had no time to fix bugs. Some are still can be present, but since mostly it works as it should, I&amp;rsquo;m releasing to stable branch.
Download stable 1.4 based on Telegram Desktop 2.7.1 Windows Supports Windows 7 and higher. 32-bit installer 32-bit portable 64-bit installer 64-bit portable Linux Supports Ubuntu 16.04 and higher. AppImage Alternative options Please note that update can be delayed.</description></item><item><title>New site is now live!</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/new-site/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:20:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/new-site/</guid><description>For a long time this site was abandoned. It featured old releases, old feature list&amp;hellip; and that&amp;rsquo;s it. It was pretty much a placeholder, than something useful.
But I think it&amp;rsquo;s time to give it a new look and content. So, welcome to the new site.
Instead of Jekyll, used in GitHub Pages by default, I decided to go with Hugo and modified port of HTML5UP&amp;rsquo;s Alpha theme. See the source code if you want to fit it for yourself.</description></item><item><title>Download Kotatogram Desktop</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/download/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/download/</guid><description>Stable version Latest is 1.4.8 (based on Telegram Desktop 3.3) Windows Supports Windows 7 and higher. 32-bit installer 32-bit portable 64-bit installer 64-bit portable Linux Supports Ubuntu 18.04 and higher. AppImage Alternative options FlatHub page Repology page macOS Supports macOS 10.15 and higher. Download Beta version Latest is 1.4.9 (based on Telegram Desktop 3.5.2) Windows Supports Windows 7 and higher. 32-bit installer 32-bit portable 64-bit installer 64-bit portable Linux Supports Ubuntu 18.</description></item><item><title>Local folders</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/features/local-folders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/features/local-folders/</guid><description>Warning: This feature currently only in beta.
Change log For a long time users have been requested folders, and Telegram made them. But of course, folders have limitations:
Folder count: no more than 10 Folder name length: no more than 12 symbols Chat count: 100 explicitly added (including pinned), 100 explicitly excluded Icons: 23 items Filters: chat type, enabled notifications, unread, non-archived Local folders have additional features and they have some limitations removed.</description></item><item><title>Test versions</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/faq/test-versions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/faq/test-versions/</guid><description>&amp;lt; Back to FAQ
What are the test versions? Will they have auto-updates? Can I use my existing Kotatogram Desktop profile? How to report a bug in test version? How to disable debug logs? Where to download test version? What are the test versions? Test versions are experimental pre-release versions of Kotatogram Desktop. They needed to test specific changes that can be possibly made in Kotatogram Desktop.
Keep in mind that all changes in the test versions are not final and there is no guarantee that they will be made in Kotatogram stable branch.</description></item></channel></rss>