<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kotatogram Desktop</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Kotatogram Desktop</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:20:00 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kotatogram.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New site is now live!</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/new-site/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:20:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/blog/new-site/</guid><description>For a long time this site was abandoned. It featured old releases, old feature list&amp;hellip; and that&amp;rsquo;s it. It was pretty much a placeholder, than something useful.
But I think it&amp;rsquo;s time to give it a new look and content. So, welcome to the new site.
Instead of Jekyll, used in GitHub Pages by default, I decided to go with Hugo and modified port of HTML5UP&amp;rsquo;s Alpha theme. See the source code if you want to fit it for yourself.</description></item><item><title>Download Kotatogram Desktop</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/download/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/download/</guid><description>Stable version Latest is 1.3.5 (based on Telegram Desktop 2.1.4) Windows Supports Windows 7 and higher. Installer Portable Linux Supports Ubuntu 16.04 and higher. Static 64-bit binary AppImage Snap Alternative options FlatHub page Repology page macOS Coming soon! Beta version Latest is 1.3.9 (based on Telegram Desktop 2.3.2) Windows Supports Windows 7 and higher. Installer Portable Linux Supports Ubuntu 16.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/faq/</guid><description>Here tackled some questions that asked pretty frequently.
When update? Will ghost mode/blocked users ignore be made? Will Android version be made? My anti-virus detects Kotatogram as a malware! Is it true that account can be banned because of unofficial client usage? Do you have any plans to monetize Kotatogram? When update? I&amp;rsquo;m trying not to tell exact dates, because usually I fit into them only when everything is ready.</description></item><item><title>Local folders</title><link>https://kotatogram.github.io/features/local-folders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kotatogram.github.io/features/local-folders/</guid><description>Warning: This feature currently only in beta.
Change log For a long time users have been requested folders, and Telegram made them. But of course, folders have limitations:
Folder count: no more than 10 Folder name length: no more than 12 symbols Chat count: 100 explicitly added (including pinned), 100 explicitly excluded Icons: 23 items Filters: chat type, enabled notifications, unread, non-archived Local folders have additional features and they have some limitations removed.</description></item></channel></rss>